{
    "id": "bb0b81af1dfa4fb69ee484758f68e6d0",
    "title": "Beginner Level Prepositions Worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4bed2d7966eb4d80bbd3c435d6d95bf6",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise For Beginners",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Little Jack Horner sat ……………….. a corner.",
                    "description": "We use 'in' to indicate position in a three-dimensional space. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The lion and the unicorn fought …………………. the crown.",
                    "description": "They didn't fight with the crown. That means they didn't use the crown as a weapon. They fought because they both wanted the crown. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "for",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. the street, the Piper stepped.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In",
                        "Into",
                        "On"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She sat ………………… the fire, and told me a tale.",
                    "description": "By can mean 'near'. Besides means 'in addition'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "with",
                        "besides"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They all ran ………………….. the farmer’s wife, who cut off their tails with a carving knife.",
                    "description": "To run after somebody is to pursue them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "into",
                        "for",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They rise ………………….. the morning lark, and labor till almost dark.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "with",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I bring fresh showers ..................... the thirsting flowers from the seas and the streams.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She laid her arms ………………….. her breast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He swore ………………… the Nine Gods.",
                    "description": "We swear by something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We go away ............................ three weeks every summer.",
                    "description": "For indicates duration since shows the starting point.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Come and see us ............................ Christmas day.",
                    "description": "We use on to talk about one day of the holiday.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will phone you ...................... 30",
                    "description": "We use 'at' with clock times.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}